Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- Clippings, 1959-2000; 26; 7.25 linear feet Boxes: 148 - 168 Folders: 1420 - 1639
  - Scenic Hudson, September 2000 (Folder 1452, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, October 2000 (Folder 1453, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, November 2000 (Folder 1454, Box 151)
  - Scenic Hudson, 2000 (Folder 1455, Box 151)
  - Power Plants; October, November, and December 1999 (Folder 1456, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, January 2000 (Folder 1457, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, February 2000 (Folder 1458, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, March 2000 (Folder 1459, Box 151)
  - Power Plants; April, May and June 2000 (Folder 1460, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, July 2000 (Folder 1461, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, August 2000 (Folder 1462, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, September 2000 (Folder 1463, Box 151)
  - Power Plants, Oct.-Dec. 2000 (Folder 1464, Box 151)
  - Development, January 2000 (Folder 1465, Box 152)
  - Development, February 2000 (Folder 1466, Box 152)
  - Development, March 2000 (Folder 1467, Box 152)
  - Development, April 2000 (Folder 1468, Box 152)
  - Development, May 2000 (Folder 1469, Box 152)
  - Development, June 2000 (Folder 1470, Box 152)
  - Development, July 2000 (Folder 1471, Box 152)
  - Development, August 2000 (Folder 1472, Box 152)
  - Development, September 2000 (Folder 1473, Box 152)
  - Development, October 2000 (Folder 1474, Box 152)
  - Development, November 2000 (Folder 1475, Box 152)
  - Development, December 2000 (Folder 1476, Box 152)
  - Development, Misc. 2000 (Folder 1477, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee; August, November and December 1999 (Folder 1478, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, Jan.-Feb. 2000 (Folder 1479, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, April-May 2000 (Folder 1480, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, June-July 2000 (Folder 1481, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, August 2000 (Folder 1482, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, September 2000 (Folder 1483, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, October 2000 (Folder 1484, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, November 2000 (Folder 1485, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, December 2000 (Folder 1486, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee, Misc. 2000 (Folder 1487, Box 152)
  - Cara Lee; Feb.-March 2001 (Folder 1488, Box 152)
  - Cell Towers, Jan.-July, 1999 (Folder 1489, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, July-Dec. 1999 (Folder 1490, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, January 2000 (Folder 1491, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, February 2000 (Folder 1492, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, March 2000 (Folder 1493, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, April 2000 (Folder 1494, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, May 2000 (Folder 1495, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, June-July 2000 (Folder 1496, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, August 2000 (Folder 1497, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, September 2000 (Folder 1498, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, Oct.-Nov. 2000 (Folder 1499, Box 153)
  - Cell Towers, December 2000 (Folder 1500, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, February 2000 (Folder 1501, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, March 2000 (Folder 1502, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, April 2000 (Folder 1503, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, May 2000 (Folder 1504, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, June 2000 (Folder 1505, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, July 2000 (Folder 1506, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, August 2000 (Folder 1507, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, September 2000 (Folder 1508, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, October 2000 (Folder 1509, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, November 2000 (Folder 1510, Box 153)
  - Indian Point, Misc. 2000 (Folder 1511, Box 153)
  - PCB’s; Jan.-April 2000 (Folder 1512, Box 154)
  - PCB’s; Sept.-Oct. 2000 (Folder 1513, Box 154)
  - PCB’s; October, November and December 2000 (Folder 1514, Box 154)
  - Greenway; January, February and March 2000 (Folder 1515, Box 155)
  - Greenway; May-June 2000 (Folder 1516, Box 155)
  - Greenway; July-Dec. 2000 (Folder 1517, Box 155)
  - Con Ed, 1968-1971 (Folder 1518, Box 156)
  - Con Ed, 1968-1971 (Folder 1519, Box 156)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 2000 (Folder 1520, Box 156)
  - Mining, 1999-2000 (Folder 1521, Box 156)
  - Mt. Beacon, 2000 (Folder 1522, Box 156)
  - Waste Removal, 2000 (Folder 1523, Box 156)
  - West Nile, 2000 (Folder 1524, Box 156)
  - Yonkers, 2000 (Folder 1525, Box 156)
  - Zoning, 2000 (Folder 1526, Box 156)
  - Andy Bicking, 1999-2000 (Folder 1527, Box 157)
  - Debbie Gross, 1999 (Folder 1528, Box 157)
  - Margery Groten, 1999-2000 (Folder 1529, Box 157)
  - Seth McKee, 1999-2000 (Folder 1530, Box 157)
  - Warren Reiss, 1999-2000 (Folder 1531, Box 157)
  - Steve Rosenberg, 1999-2000 (Folder 1532, Box 157)
  - Rita Shaheen, 1999-2000 (Folder 1533, Box 157)
  - Hank Stebbins, 1999-2000 (Folder 1534, Box 157)
  - Michelle Terwilliger, 1999-2000 (Folder 1535, Box 157)
  - Transportation, 1999-2000 (Folder 1536, Box 157)
  - Transportation, 1999-2000 (Folder 1537, Box 157)
  - Hazel Westney, 1999 (Folder 1538, Box 157)
  - Beacon, 1999-2000 (Folder 1539, Box 158)
  - BesiCorp. Recycling Plant, 1999-2000 (Folder 1540, Box 158)
  - Chip Fabrication, 1999-2000 (Folder 1541, Box 158)
  - Dia Center, 1999-2000 (Folder 1542, Box 158)
  - Esopus, 1999-2000 (Folder 1543, Box 158)
  - Great River Sweep. 1999-2000 (Folder 1544, Box 158)
  - Scenic Hudson Ads, 1999-2000 (Folder 1545, Box 158)
  - Ned Sullivan, 2000 (Folder 1546, Box 158)
  - Clausland, 1999-2000 (Folder 1547, Box 159)
  - Commercial Fishing, 1999 (Folder 1548, Box 159)
  - Countryside Exchange, 1999 (Folder 1549, Box 159)
  - Hazardous Waste, 1999-2000 (Folder 1550, Box 159)
  - Irvington, 1999-2000 (Folder 1551, Box 159)
  - Land Preservation, 2000 (Folder 1552, Box 159)
  - Mercury, 2000 (Folder 1553, Box 159)
  - Newburgh, 2000 (Folder 1554, Box 159)
  - Piermont, 2000 (Folder 1555, Box 159)
  - Pollution, 2000 (Folder 1556, Box 159)
  - Poughkeepsie Railroad Bridge, 2000 (Folder 1557, Box 159)
  - Recycling, 1999-2000 (Folder 1558, Box 159)
  - Restore vs. Rebuild, 1999 (Folder 1559, Box 159)
  - Riverfront Access, 1999 (Folder 1560, Box 159)
  - Riverkeeper, 1999-2000 (Folder 1561, Box 159)
  - Route 120, 1999 (Folder 1562, Box 159)
  - Smart Growth, 1999-2000 (Folder 1563, Box 159)
  - Sour Mountain, 1999-2000 (Folder 1564, Box 159)
  - Tallix, 1999 (Folder 1565, Box 159)
  - Tourism, 2000 (Folder 1566, Box 159)
  - Beacon, 1999-2000 (Folder 1567, Box 160)
  - Environmental Education, 1999-2000 (Folder 1568, Box 160)
  - Farmland, 1999-2000 (Folder 1569, Box 160)
  - Hudson River, 2000 (Folder 1570, Box 160)
  - Indian Point, 2000 (Folder 1571, Box 160)
  - Sterling Forest, 1999-2000 (Folder 1572, Box 160)
  - aterfront Development, 2000 (Folder 1573, Box 160)
  - Wetlands, 2000 (Folder 1574, Box 160)
  - Black Creek, 1999-2000 (Folder 1575, Box 161)
  - Deborah M. DeWan, 1999-2000 (Folder 1576, Box 161)
  - Greenway, 2000 (Folder 1577, Box 161)
  - Hudson River Institute, 2000 (Folder 1578, Box 161)
  - Legislature, 1999-2000 (Folder 1579, Box 161)
  - Metro North, 1999-2000 (Folder 1580, Box 161)
  - MTBE, 1999-2000 (Folder 1581, Box 161)
  - Newburgh, 2000 (Folder 1582, Box 161)
  - Poughkeepsie Waterfront, 1999-2000 (Folder 1583, Box 161)
  - Red Hook, 2000 (Folder 1584, Box 161)
  - St. Lawrence Cement Plant, 2000 (Folder 1585, Box 161)
  - Air Quality, 1999-2000 (Folder 1586, Box 162)
  - Jeff Anzevino, 2000 (Folder 1587, Box 162)
  - Aquarium, 2000 (Folder 1588, Box 162)
  - Burger Hill Park, 2000 (Folder 1589, Box 162)
  - Candlelight Vigil, 2000 (Folder 1590, Box 162)
  - Jonathan Chu, 2000 (Folder 1591, Box 162)
  - Farmland, 2000 (Folder 1592, Box 162)
  - Foundry Cove, 2000 (Folder 1593, Box 162)
  - Havestraw, 2000 (Folder 1594, Box 162)
  - Madam Brett Homestead, 2000 (Folder 1595, Box 162)
  - Olana, 1999-2000 (Folder 1596, Box 162)
  - Pipeline, 2000 (Folder 1597, Box 162)
  - Poets Walk, 2000 (Folder 1598, Box 162)
  - Sprawl, 2000 (Folder 1599, Box 162)
  - Superfund, 1999-2000 (Folder 1600, Box 162)
  - Tappan Zee Bridge, 2000 (Folder 1601, Box 162)
  - Marion Trieste, 2000 (Folder 1602, Box 162)
  - Water Quality, 1999-2000 (Folder 1603, Box 162)
  - Athens, 2000 (Folder 1604, Box 163)
  - Hannaford, 2000 (Folder 1605, Box 163)
  - Historical Hudson Valley, 2000 (Folder 1606, Box 163)
  - Hudson River Estuary Plan, 2000 (Folder 1607, Box 163)
  - Hyde Park, 2000 (Folder 1608, Box 163)
  - Open Space, 2000 (Folder 1609, Box 163)
  - Scenic Hudson, 2000 (Folder 1610, Box 163)
  - Jim Detjen (Folder 1611, Box 164)
  - Editorials (Folder 1612, Box 164)
  - Fish In Hudson (Folder 1613, Box 164)
  - PASNY (Folder 1614, Box 164)
  - David Sive (Folder 1615, Box 164)
  - Storm King (Folder 1616, Box 164)
  - SHPC Paste Up of News Clips (no date) (Folder 1617, Box 165)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings (no dates) (Folder 1618, Box 165)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 2000 (Folder 1619, Box 165)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 2000 (Folder 1620, Box 165)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 2000 (Folder 1621, Box 165)
  - Scrap Book 1930s (Folder 1622, Box 166)
  - Nuclear 1969 - 1970 (Folder 1623, Box 167)
  - Nuclear May 1971 - July 1973 (Folder 1624, Box 167)
  - Nuclear October 197? - June 1973 (Folder 1625, Box 167)
  - Nuclear 1974 (Folder 1626, Box 167)
  - Nuclear 1975 (Folder 1627, Box 168)
  - Nuclear 1976 (Folder 1628, Box 168)
  - Nuclear June 1976 (Folder 1629, Box 168)
  - Miscellaneous from Scrap Books, fallen out (Folder 1630, Box 168)
  - Federal Legislation (Folder 1631, Box 168)
  - Biology (Folder 1632, Box 168)
  - Taxation (Folder 1633, Box 168)
  - Voting Records (Folder 1634, Box 168)
  - County (Folder 1635, Box 168)
  - Garbage (Folder 1636, Box 168)
  - Land Preservation (Folder 1637, Box 168)
  - Museums (Folder 1638, Box 168)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 1639, Box 168)
- Photographs, 1975-1999; 27; 2.67 linear feet Boxes: 169 - 176 Folders: 1640 - 1736
  Photographic documentation of various events hosted and sponsored by Scenic Hudson, Inc. Also contains photographs of various economically endangered sites.
  - Bronck Museum, 1975 (Folder 1640, Box 169)
  - Pancake Breakfast, 1978 (Folder 1641, Box 169)
  - Hudson River Field Trip, 1978 (Folder 1642, Box 169)
  - Storm King Hike, 1980 (Folder 1643, Box 169)
  - Hudson River Settlement, 1980 (Folder 1644, Box 169)
  - Ferry Sloop Lecture, 1980 (Folder 1645, Box 169)
  - ELP Boat Ride, 1981 (Folder 1646, Box 169)
  - Little Stony Point Breakfast, 1981 (Folder 1647, Box 169)
  - 20th Anniversary at Lyndhurst, 1983 (Folder 1648, Box 169)
  - Hamilton Fish; Visit to Washington’s Headquarters (Newburgh), 1985 (Folder 1649, Box 169)
  - Statue Of Liberty Celebration, 1986 (Folder 1650, Box 169)
  - New Response Art Exhibit, 1986 (Folder 1651, Box 169)
  - EQBA Work Meeting, 1986 (Folder 1652, Box 169)
  - “Water for Millions, At What Cost?” 06/04/1987 (Folder 1653, Box 169)
  - 25th Anniversary Train Ride, 10/15/1988 (Folder 1654, Box 169)
  - Storm King Hike, 1988 (Folder 1655, Box 169)
  - Press Conference; Empire State Building, 1989 (Folder 1656, Box 169)
  - First Greenway Council; Mills Mansion, 04/28/1989 (Folder 1657, Box 169)
  - Challenge on the Hudson, 1990 (Folder 1658, Box 170)
  - Challenge on the Hudson, 1990 (Folder 1659, Box 170)
  - Hudson River Quilt, January 1990 (Folder 1660, Box 170)
  - Light House Celebration, 10/01/1990 (Folder 1661, Box 170)
  - Eve’s Point Celebration, 10/30/1990 (Folder 1662, Box 170)
  - Regatta, 1991 (Folder 1663, Box 170)
  - Water Symposium, 1991 (Folder 1664, Box 170)
  - Greenway Council, April 1991 (Folder 1665, Box 170)
  - Open Space Hearings, January 1992 (Folder 1666, Box 171)
  - Hermes Benefit, 02/25/1992 (Folder 1667, Box 171)
  - Greenway Trail Benefit, 03/07/1992 (Folder 1668, Box 171)
  - Greenway Signing; Mills Mansion, 04/22/1992 (Folder 1669, Box 171)
  - River Champ Reception, 06/26/1992 (Folder 1670, Box 171)
  - Lehigh Cement Field Trip, 08/21/1992 (Folder 1671, Box 171)
  - Beacon Waterfront Revitalization, September 1992 (Folder 1672, Box 171)
  - Riverfront Cleanup, 09/19/1992 (Folder 1673, Box 171)
  - Four Mile Point Celebration, 09/30/1992 (Folder 1674, Box 171)
  - Mystery Point Beach Tour, November 1992 (Folder 1675, Box 171)
  - Environmental Assistance Fund, 04/01/1993 (Folder 1676, Box 172)
  - Hudson River Cruise, 05/26/1993 (Folder 1677, Box 172)
  - Greenway Conference, 06/02/1993 (Folder 1678, Box 172)
  - National Trails Day, 06/06/1993 (Folder 1679, Box 172)
  - 30th Anniversary Celebration, 06/15/1993 (Folder 1680, Box 172)
  - Birdathon Donation for Sleightsburg Spit, 06/16/1993 (Folder 1681, Box 172)
  - Ramshorn Re-opening, 06/22/1993 (Folder 1682, Box 172)
  - Pancake Breakfast, 10/02/1993 (Folder 1683, Box 172)
  - Olana View shed Tour, 09/18/1993 (Folder 1684, Box 172)
  - Stewart Airport Conference, 10/26/1993 (Folder 1685, Box 172)
  - Esopus Environmental Center, 11/1992 (Folder 1686, Box 172)
  - Riverchamp Reception, 11/29/1993 (Folder 1687, Box 172)
  - Senator Moynihan Visit to Tarrytown for Waterfront Park, 1994 (Folder 1688, Box 173)
  - GQ Magazine Macy’s Event, 02/24/1994 (Folder 1689, Box 173)
  - Chevron Corp.&Times Mirror Magazines Conservation Award; 05/18/1994 (Folder 1690, Box 173)
  - Spirit of the Hudson Gala; The Plaza Hotel, 06/01/1994 (Folder 1691, Box 173)
  - Landscape Architecture Conference, 06/18/1994 (Folder 1692, Box 173)
  - Pancake Breakfast, 09/23/1994 (Folder 1693, Box 173)
  - Hyde Park Ceremony For Historic Dedication, 11/01/1994 (Folder 1694, Box 173)
  - River Champion Reception, 11/28/1994 (Folder 1695, Box 173)
  - Spirit of the River Gala; The Pierre Hotel, 1995 (Folder 1696, Box 173)
  - Bruce Babbitt’s Visit, 08/11/1995 (Folder 1697, Box 173)
  - Transportation Forum, October 1995 (Folder 1698, Box 173)
  - River Champion Reception; Sotheby’s, November 1995 (Folder 1699, Box 173)
  - Pancake Breakfast, 1996 (Folder 1700, Box 173)
  - Press Conference in Alabama, February 1996 (Folder 1701, Box 173)
  - Land Trust Retreat; Mohonk Mountain House, February 9-10, 1996 (Folder 1702, Box 173)
  - PCB Conference, 05/30/1996 (Folder 1703, Box 173)
  - Spirit of the River Gala, 06/12/1996 (Folder 1704, Box 173)
  - Foundry Cove Cleanup, 04/26/1997 (Folder 1706, Box 174)
  - Hudson River Steward Society Tea, 05/18/1997 (Folder 1707, Box 174)
  - Groundbreaking Ceremony; Irvington, 05/19/1997 (Folder 1708, Box 174)
  - Esty Stowell Trail Opening at Museum of the Hudson Highlands, June 1997 (Folder 1709, Box 174)
  - Spirit of the River Gala at the University Club, 06/18/1997 (Folder 1710, Box 174)
  - Sterling Forest Press Conference, 08/14/1997 (Folder 1711, Box 174)
  - Heritage Initiatives, 08/15/1997 (Folder 1712, Box 174)
  - Pancake Breakfast, 09/21/1997 (Folder 1713, Box 174)
  - PCB Briefing; Olana, 09/25/1997 (Folder 1714, Box 174)
  - Fishkill Ridge Hike, 10/04/1997 (Folder 1715, Box 174)
  - Young Friends Hike Storm King Mountain, 10/18/1997 (Folder 1716, Box 174)
  - Poet’s Walk Festival, 10/19/1997 (Folder 1717, Box 174)
  - Poets Walk Festival, 1998 (Folder 1718, Box 175)
  - Poets Walk Festival, 1998 (Folder 1719, Box 175)
  - Poets Walk Festival, 1998 (Folder 1720, Box 175)
  - Madam Brett, Mill Park Clean Up, 1998 (Folder 1721, Box 175)
  - Spirit of the River Gala, 1998 (Folder 1722, Box 175)
  - Estuary Action Program, April 1998 (Folder 1723, Box 175)
  - Steamboat Dock; Verplank, 04/21/1998 (Folder 1724, Box 175)
  - Great River Sweep, May 9-17, 1998 (Folder 1725, Box 175)
  - Young Friends Autumn Celebration, 1998 (Folder 1726, Box 175)
  - Mt. Beacon Trail Masters Event w/ Young Friends of Scenic Hudson, 10/24/1998 (Folder 1727, Box 176)
  - Winter Warm-Up; Foundry Cove, 12/05/1998 (Folder 1728, Box 176)
  - Misc. Pictures of Frank and Andrew Mason (Folder 1729, Box 176)
  - Misc. Pictures of Phyllis Harriman, Crispin Connery and Cabot Connery (Folder 1730, Box 176)
  - Whooping Crane Awards, Tavern on the Green (Folder 1731, Box 176)
  - Storm King Mountain (Folder 1732, Box 176)
  - Misc. Pictures (no dates) (Folder 1733, Box 176)
  - Misc. Pictures of the Hudson (Folder 1734, Box 176)
  - Misc. Pictures of Carl Carmer (no dates) (Folder 1735, Box 176)
  - Negatives; Storm King (Folder 1736, Box 176)
- Hanging Photographs, 28; 1 linear foot Box: 177 Folder: 1737
  Hanging photograph
  Hanging Storage
  - Scenic Hudson Collage (Folder 1737, Box 177)
- Audio-Visual Oversized Materials, 29; 4.33 linear feet Boxes: 178 - 197 Folders: 1738 - 1930
  Audiotapes, videocassettes, templates, scrapbooks, and slides gathered and/or created by Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  - Misc. Oversized Documents, 1992-1994; 29.1
    Layouts, state decree, templates
    - Misc. Original Layouts (not poster board) (Folder 1738, Box 178)
    - State of New York Decree (Folder 1739, Box 178)
    - Original Scenic Hudson Stationary Template (Folder 1740, Box 178)
    - Large Photograph of Bear Mountain Bridge (Folder 1741, Box 178)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Back Cover/Front Cover (Folder 1742, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 2/Page 3 (Folder 1743, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 4/Page 5 (Folder 1744, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 6/Page 7 (Folder 1745, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 8/Page 9 (Folder 1746, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 10/Page 11 (Folder 1747, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 12/Page 13 (Folder 1748, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 14/Page 15 (Folder 1749, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 16/Page 17 (Folder 1750, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 18/Page 19 (Folder 1751, Box 179)
    - SH Annual Report, 07/01/1993 - 06/30/1994, Page 20/Page 21 (Folder 1752, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson’s Quarter of Century Achievements (Folder 1753, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 1 (Folder 1754, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 2 (Folder 1755, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 3 (Folder 1755, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 4 (Folder 1756, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 5 (Folder 1757, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 6 (Folder 1758, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 7 (Folder 1759, Box 179)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1992, Page 8 (Folder 1760, Box 179)
  - Audio Cassette Tapes, 1973-1999; 29.2
    Audio Casset Tapes
    - Catskill Aqueduct Series Special Features Unit, October 1973 (Folder 1761, Box 180)
    - Christopher Reeve Interview 03/081994 (Folder 1762, Box 180)
    - Davis, Lydia Adams Demo Tape (Folder 1763, Box 180)
    - Hudson River Estuarine Sanctuary (Folder 1764, Box 181)
    - Harper’s Article (Folder 1765, Box 181)
    - Hudson Valley Perspective WKIP 96.9 10/27/1991 (Folder 1766, Box 181)
    - Great River Sloop 02/11/1999 (Folder 1767, Box 182)
    - Interview with N/S, The Environment Show (Folder 1768, Box 182)
    - Norman, Lawrence, Patterson,&Farrell, Inc. (Folder 1769, Box 182)
    - Scenic Hudson Board Meeting, June 16 (A1) (Folder 1770, Box 183)
    - Scenic Hudson Board Meeting, June 16 (B1) (Folder 1771, Box 183)
    - Scenic Hudson “Chat”: 60 Stereo, King Harvest Communications (Folder 1772, Box 183)
    - Scenic Hudson Spots “Journey,” “Chat,” “Questions” (Folder 1773, Box 184)
    - Scenic Hudson “Noise”; 60 (Folder 1774, Box 184)
    - Scenic Hudson WHUD LM/N 860 - 9/11 (Folder 1775, Box 184)
    - Scenic Hudson WHUD 60 - 9/91 (Folder 1776, Box 185)
    - Solar Energy Seminar (Folder 1777, Box 185)
    - Stewart Airport (Folder 1778, Box 185)
    - TGR’s PSA’s 03/01/1991 (Folder 1779, Box 186)
    - WHUD-WLMA News Report 09/11/1991, Stewart News Forum (Folder 1780, Box 186)
  - VHS, 29.3
    Beta Cam SP and Film Reels, 16mm Color Film, Scenic Hudson Film Production, Misc VHS, Conference Tapes, ¾ Inch Tapes
    - America Cole PSA 4 @ 3:30 (1/4 inch audio tape; small reel) (Folder 1781, Box 187)
    - America Cole PSA 4 @ 3:30 (1/4 inch audio tape; large reel) (Folder 1782, Box 187)
    - American Heritage River Designation at West Point 0798 (Folder 1783, Box 187)
    - Pataki, Master- 1 Minute (Folder 1784, Box 187)
    - Riverfront Renaissance, The Beacon Story, June 11, 2000 (Folder 1785, Box 187)
    - Harriman Dub Tape (Folder 1786, Box 187)
    - Scenic Hudson Honors the Harrimans (Folder 1787, Box 187)
    - Peter Stern’s Violin at Storm King (Folder 1788, Box 187)
    - Sauer Dub Tape (Folder 1789, Box 187)
    - Time for the River (Folder 1790, Box 188)
    - Farmland Forever (Folder 1791, Box 189)
    - Scenic Hudson Saving the River (Folder 1792, Box 189)
    - Scenic Hudson Honoring John Winthrop Aldrich (Folder 1793, Box 189)
    - The Rockefellers: Honor Earth (Folder 1794, Box 189)
    - Scenic Hudson honoring The Osborn Family (Folder 1795, Box 189)
    - CBR 12/02/1993 (Folder 1796, Box 190)
    - The Facts about the Sour Mountain Mine Project (Folder 1797, Box 190)
    - “It Ain’t easy Being Green” (Folder 1798, Box 190)
    - The Hudson River PCB Story: A Toxic Heritage (Folder 1799, Box 190)
    - Mount Beacon Acquisition, WTZA 10/6/1992 (Folder 1800, Box 190)
    - Hudson Valley Six (a) (Folder 1801, Box 190)
    - Hudson Valley Six (b) (Folder 1802, Box 190)
    - Hudson Valley 6, Montfort/ Reiss Interview (Folder 1803, Box 190)
    - Hudson Valley 6- Sour Mountain Project Parts 1 and 2 (Folder 1804, Box 190)
    - RNN Presentation Video- Pataki Speech (Folder 1805, Box 190)
    - Stewart Airport (Folder 1806, Box 190)
    - Hudson Valley 6 (c) (Folder 1807, Box 190)
    - River Conference Tape 1 AM (Folder 1808, Box 191)
    - River Conference Tape 2 AM (Folder 1809, Box 191)
    - River Conference Tape 3 AM (Folder 1810, Box 191)
    - River Conference Tape 4 AM (Folder 1811, Box 191)
    - River Conference Tape 5 AM (Folder 1812, Box 192)
    - River Conference Tape 6 AM (Folder 1813, Box 192)
    - River Conference Tape 7 AM (Folder 1814, Box 192)
    - Misc. Not labeled Tape (Folder 1815, Box 192)
    - Scenic Hudson: A Celebration of Anniversaries in the Hudson Valley (Folder 1816, Box 193)
    - The Lost Mountain Railways (Folder 1817, Box 193)
    - ECONEWS #1512 (Folder 1818, Box 193)
    - Environmental PSA Scenic Hudson’s: 60 vers.&: 30 edited vers. (Folder 1819, Box 193)
  - Slides, 29.4
    35 millimeter Slides; 2 ¼ inch Slides
    - Sheet 1 (Folder 1820, Box 194)
    - Sheet 2 (Folder 1821, Box 194)
    - Sheet 3 (Folder 1822, Box 194)
    - Sheet 4 (Folder 1823, Box 194)
    - SPHC Commentary for Slide Show “The Hudson River& Its Painters” (Folder 1824, Box 194)
    - Slide Show, Sykes, Rowe, Reese, etc. (Folder 1825, Box 194)
    - Pringle Slides (Folder 1826, Box 195)
    - Scenic Hudson Slide Show (Folder 1827, Box 195)
    - Stewart Noyes Slides (Folder 1828, Box 195)
  - Artifacts, 1936; 29.5
    Scenic Hudson Seal Stamp; Banner
    - Paper Stamp (Produces embossed seal that reads, “The Hudson Valley Conservation Society 1936 New York.”) (Folder 1829, Box 196)
    - Challenge of the Hudson Banner (Folder 1830, Box 197)